I didn't burn down the factory!
I knew they'd include you
in the investigation.
And I couldn't risk them destroying you.
None of this is your fault, dear.
I know he's the vermin
that's infesting La Familia.
Are you having someone tail me?
I need to know the truth.
Those are personal details.
I can't help but be suspicious.
My resignation letter.
Diana, I can't stay in a place…
where no one trusts me.
Ricardo.
Diana.
Diana…
Hi.
Diana, this is Sandra.
Ricardo's ex.
I hope I'm not interrupting.
I was just passing by.
No, not at all.
Actually, we haven't even ordered yet, so…
Why don't you join us?
I'll pass.
Please join us.
I've heard so much about you.
Really?
Diana, Sandra's here
because she found out about…
my mother.
And she heard that I'm selling my house.
Yes, I heard.
I feel sorry for Ma'am Ester.
But, anyway, um…
The property is under Ricardo's name, and…
since we're both investors,
we were just discussing
how we'd split the proceeds
once the property is sold.
You're selling your house?
Yes. I guess because he's so affected
by his loss,
he might want to go back to Indonesia.
By the way, um…
what are you doing here?
I was really just passing by.
There's something I need
to buy from this restaurant.
I didn't know you'd be here.
Please join us.
Please.
I need to go to the restroom.
I needed to go to the restroom, too.
Why?
Nothing.
I know what's going on
between you and Ricardo.
He told me.
I also know you were surprised to see me.
I'm sure Ricardo doesn't
talk about me much.
You're right.
Well, that's how Ricardo is.
He's very private about his personal life.
All I know is that you two were
never really together.
Except that you became
the mother of his child.
I just didn't know you were still
seeing each other,
that… you were still friends.
You've got it all wrong, okay?
I won't be a problem for you, I promise.
Ricardo's really just a good friend.
That's it. That's all there is to it.
I don't think you need
to explain yourself to me.
Besides…
Ricardo's leaving. Right?
You're not going to stop him?
I understand how you feel, Diana,
because I'm a woman, too.
Whatever happened between
Ricardo and me back then,
that's all it was.
It didn't work out for us as a couple,
but he's the best person I know.
And I really do hope that someday,
he finds someone who'll love him
the way he deserves.
Because he's an amazing guy.
And he deserves to be
with the best person.
Diana!
Diana.
I thought you were joining us?
Uh, no, I need to go.
Diana, wait.
Why are you following me?
Didn't I tell you that
if there's something
you want to know about me,
you can ask me directly?
I'll tell you the truth.
I'm sorry. I don't…
I don't know what's gotten into me.
I just want all of this to be over.
Then let's end it.
Whatever's been bothering me about you.
Diana, I've shown you everything
you need to see.
You're the only one
who refuses to believe me.
I'm not doing anything wrong to you.
I really do love you. That's all.
But you can't make me pay
for everyone who's ever hurt you.
You know what hurts?
The part where you say you trust me,
but you're investigating me?
I'm sorry.
Instead of asking me for the truth.
I thought what we had was real.
Maybe it's time for me to distance myself,
so you won't be confused anymore.
I'll just use my remaining month
as vacation leave.
So you won't have to worry anymore.
This is the last day you'll see me.
Thank you for everything.
Are you waiting for someone?
Aww, Ricardo resigned.
Hmm.
Call Mr. Borja and the rest of the team.
I already told them before I came in here.
What about Ricardo?
Hmm, should I follow up with him?
Don't you have anything to do
in this meeting?
Why don't you make yourself useful?
I can't blame that guy.
Because who could last in La Familia?
Or with you?
Hmm.
Do you want some tea?
Hm?
I'll get you some. Want some?
Good afternoon.
Did you call for me?
You can go.
Um… You're needed for the PR presentation
of Burger City later.
I've already handed
everything over to the team.
Burger City requested
specifically for you.
After all, you spearheaded the campaign.
And when I spoke to your team earlier,
I could tell they weren't ready.
They weren't confident.
Okay. I'll talk to my team now.
Ricardo, I need you.
I mean to…
be here in the meeting.
After all, you're still serving
your 30-day notice.
Just attend the meeting.
Okay.
Under the law, an employee
who engages in secret transactions
against the company
can be terminated on those grounds.
This should take effect immediately,
Sir Teddy.
I have shares in this company.
Being an employee and being a shareholder
are separate matters under the law.
So you still retain your shares.
It depends on what's stated
in La Familia's buyback clause
in the bylaws.
Thank you for attending the meeting.
Actually, I wanted to talk to you, too.
Diana!
-Let's talk.
-Teddy?
-Sir Teddy. Sir Teddy!
-No, no, no!
-I need to talk to her!
-Teddy! Teddy.
The investigation went through
the proper process.
There was nothing I could do.
If you want to appeal, get a lawyer.
We'll go through the proper process.
But for now, there's nothing I can do.
Ricardo was the one behind all of it!
Teddy, will you stop it?
-Enough.
-Sis.
I'm trying to protect you
because you're my sister.
But the truth will come out eventually.
And when it does,
I hope you won't regret this.
Everything you're doing,
I just hope it's not too late.
-Teddy, just leave.
-Shut up.
I'm not talking to you.
I'll expose who you really are.
Sir.
-Just come with us, sir.
-Let me go!
-I said let me go! Why are you--
-Don't worry.
-I'll handle this.
-Back off!
Let me go!
Mom. Mom, are you okay?
Are you sure with your decision
about Uncle Teddy?
His claims seem valid
and he can back them up.
This isn't easy for me, too.
But I think it's for the best
that he isn't in La Familia for now.
Maybe he needs to stand on his own.
Maybe this is what he needs.
I'll check on Ms. D, okay?
-Let me go! Back off!
-Calm down, sir.
-Just come with us.
-Damn it! You're hurting me!
-Sir--
-What the--
I'll make you pay for this!
-Especially you!
-Leave his things here.
Put that down.
You bastard.
You're an animal. We're not done yet.
I will come for you
and I will not stop!
I'll expose all your dirt.
I want to see you try.
You'll surely regret it.
Get him out of here.
Sorry.
-Patricia.
-Enzo.
How's Mom?
She's fine. How about you?
-How do you feel? Are you okay?
-I'm okay.
But…
But?
I saw Sir Ricardo.
He escorted Uncle Teddy out.
It's like he's having fun with it.
The way he kicked Uncle Teddy out…
he was mean.
I've never seen him like that before.
It's concerning.
You don't need to worry about it now.
He resigned.
He won't be in La Familia for long.
Okay?
Teddy just left.
Is there anything else you need from me?
Let's go out.
What?
It's too chaotic in here.
Besides, we have a lot to talk about.
What happened earlier
was a lot to take in.
I'm sure you need a break.
Diana, I don't have much time
left here in La Familia.
Oh.
"Mother and child."
Do you want it?
It's beautiful.
Excuse me.
We'll get this.
Ricardo.
Ricardo, it's two million pesos.
It's okay.
It's my gift to you.
It's a good investment.
I don't know. It's too much.
Diana.
You've been taking care of La Familia
your whole life.
Maybe it's time to put yourself first.
Take a load off your plate.
Or maybe… it's time for you to step down.
I will stay with La Familia
as long as I'm needed.
I made that promise to Dad.
It's also for Patricia's future.
You said we have something to talk about.
Yes.
Wait, let me go first.
I need to say this and go first.
Ricardo…
I'm very, very sorry about
what happened at the restaurant.
Forget it. It's fine. It's okay.
-Are you sure?
-Yes.
I invited you to go out because…
because I want to be with you
in the little time we have left together.
I want us to part
with just happy memories.
I'll miss you, Diana.
It feels nice to see you smile.
I can't even remember
the last time I experienced this.
And that song…
Mom used to always play that on the piano.
Ricardo, how have you been?
Oh, Rannie. Allan.
Diana, these are
my ex-officemates in Indonesia.
Rannie and Allan.
This is Ms. Diana Aragon.
Diana Aragon of La Familia?
Yes.
What a surprise, Ricardo.
We've never seen you go on a date.
What a sight to see you
on a date with Diana Aragon.
Am I right?
The Chairmom.
I see your fetish is a dominant woman.
Must be pretty exciting,
isn't it, Ricardo?
The Chairmom I'd like to--
-Your face.
-What did you just say?
-Easy, easy. Easy.
-Come on, say it again!
-Ricardo.
-I'll beat the hell out of you!
Easy, man.
-What?
-Ricardo.
Rannie, let's go. Let's go.
My apologies.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry about that.
I'm okay. It's okay. I'm okay.
I won't let anyone
disrespect you like that.
Diana I've never felt this way before.
I know you're used
to protecting other people.
But who will protect you?
Who will protect you when I'm gone?
Diana, if we don't feel the same way,
then I won't force this.
I'll just leave.
I won't bother you anymore.
Ricardo…
I tried to stop it.
But the truth is…
I've never felt this way before.
I'm sorry.
-Carlota. Here you go.
-Oh!
You brought the orders!
Oh, my colleagues
have been waiting for this.
There are new products in there.
Tell them about it too.
There. Of course.
Oh, after work,
can we watch a movie?
My favorite love team has a new film.
And can we have dinner at a hotel?
Oh! I think it'd be better
to spend the night there?
Is that possible?
-We can do that.
-Yay!
I'm here.
It's from Ricardo.
I know what you're thinking.
It's Sir Ricardo.
What about him?
I just noticed that
he's like a different person.
What do you mean?
When you're with him, he's calm.
He always finds a solution.
But he acts differently
when you're not around.
I understand if he's a private person
and he has things
he wants to keep to himself.
There are things we don't know about him.
How can we prove
that what he says is true?
Well, what I would always say…
be vigilant but fair.
Even Uncle Teddy is suspicious of him.
And Mom, I did my research too.
I can't find anything about his family
or his personal life.
Is that even possible?
I already met the mother of his child.
And his friends as well.
I hear you.
But let's be fair.
If you guys are suspicious of Ricardo,
then you have to have proof against him.
-Huh?
-Oh?
-What's that?
-What's happening?
What's that?
E…
Enzo!
Is there an earthquake or fire drill
scheduled today?
That's what I was wondering.
But there's none.
I'm trying to call security now.
What is that?
Let's get out of the building.
It might be a real emergency.
-Yes, yes.
-Let's go.
Let's go.
Maybe it's just a fire drill.
No, we have to get out. It might be real.
This is not right. Just hold on to me.
Oh, Ricardo.
Diana…
I may be leaving La Familia…
But I don't want to disappear
from your life.
I want to prove my love for you.
I love you so much.
And I can prove that every day.
Diana Aragon…
Will you marry me?
Diana.
Ricardo, get up.
You know that I love you so much, right?
Everything I've told you before is true.
All of that. I love you.
I love you so much.
But I'm…
I'm not at the point of marriage yet.
I can't.
I'm so sorry.
You seem relieved
that Ms. D rejected Sir Ricardo.
A marriage… should be well-thought-out.
It's not done carelessly.
Yes. I know.
But is that really the reason?
Don't you want Ms. D to be happy?
I do.
What if it's Sir Ricardo
who could make her happy?
No problem!
As long as we're certain
that Sir Ricardo is a good man.
You have a point.
I also want Ms. D to be happy.
And I do think it's too early
for her to say yes to Sir Ricardo.
What I want is…
if Mom will get another
partner in life again,
it has to be someone
who will surely not deceive
and hurt her.
Oh, Dad! Is Mom not with you?
Dad, is there a problem?
Stop what you're doing for now.
You have to help me do something.
Jena?
April!
Why is it so dark?
Did they cut off our power?
But the neighbors have lights.
Jena, April!
Where are you?
What is this?
Martin?
Carlota…
let's get married.
Why?
Isn't this what you want?
You've been waiting a long time
for us to get married.
Is that your only reason?
What other reason would I have?
Mom, what's with you?
Will you say no?
Mom, don't you want this?
No, of course, I'm saying yes!
Y-Yes.
Yes.
Yay!
-Congrats, Mom!
-Congrats, Mom! Congrats, Dad!
Patricia, Patricia!
Your Dad and I are getting married!
It seems like your marriage
with Diana won't push through.
Patricia is against it.
No one can stop my plan.
Not even Patricia.
Do you like it?
Yes, but…
It looks old, doesn't it?
The color's kind of fading.
Because it's secondhand.
What matters is…
I gave the ring to your mother.
Besides, it's pretty, Mom.
I'll start looking for a church.
Sure. You can even start tomorrow.
Wow! That's fast!
Your father's just joking.
We have to plan the wedding well
because I want it to be
very extravagant. Right?
I think it'd be better
if we have a civil wedding first.
Then we can just do
the church wedding another time.
It's like you're racing against someone.
Well, would you look at it?
I'm still the winner!
What do you mean?
Well, I'm getting married before Diana!
Mom rejected Sir Ricardo's proposal.
We're getting married!
This! I want a ball gown.
The train has to be long
and has to be filled
with Swarovski crystals.
Right? I want something that,
when the people see me walking,
they'll go,
"Oh, wow! Oh, wow, Carlota is beautiful."
-Then they'll cry, right?
-Mom! Right!
Right?
-Correct!
-I want that. Yes.
-We won't be outdone.
-Yes.
But what if Ma'am Diana said yes?
You would've gotten married
at the same time.
I know, right!
It's a good thing
she rejected Ricardo
because, if ever, my gosh!
My gosh, your sister would've had
to share her inheritance with someone.
What would happen
to the pain I endured for years
if she wouldn't inherit everything?
My gosh, Mom.
Is that what you think of Patricia?
Don't you treat her as your own child?
But no matter what you say,
I didn't give birth to her.
Besides,
if she weren't your father's daughter…
If she weren't an heiress,
I wouldn't even glance at her.
That's all she is to me.
Come on, let's check out more gowns.
-Here, Mom.
-I like that.
-It's pretty.
-I think it suits you!
I'll look slim!
Oh, what's this?
Wedding flower arrangements?
Who's getting married?
Um, me, sir.
I just got engaged, sir!
Congratulations!
Thank you.
So, when is the big day?
Very, very soon.
And, of course,
you're going to be invited, sir!
Oh, I'm sure you're very happy.
Your husband's a lucky man.
Very, very lucky, sir.
Uh, do you have any advice
coming from a married man, sir?
Well,
I'm probably not the best person to ask.
My marriage is, um…
It has a lot of problems.
I'm sure you can fix that, sir.
I've tried, you know.
But this one's not worth saving, so, um…
I'm getting a divorce.
Oh…
Oh, no…
I'm so sorry to hear that, sir.
Oh…
I'm okay.
Patricia.
Patricia! Hey. Hey.
Could you get the invitations?
The coordinator called to say
we should meet today, but…
I have a lot of work to do.
Okay?
I'll do it when my shift's done.
But, you know, it'll be quick.
You can come back here
right away if you leave now.
And pay for it too, will you?
You haven't contributed anything
to our wedding, after all.
Hm?
Mom, Mom asked me to do something.
So what?
My marriage to your father
is not important to you?
Is that it?
Patricia.
Is everything all right?
I'm fine, Enzo.
Mom, I really can't handle that today.
We're working,
and that's a personal matter.
I am asking you for such a small favor.
And yet you can't do it.
It's like we're not family.
Sorry, with all due respect…
Patricia does everything for you.
Please don't say hurtful things to her
when she does something for herself.
What did you say?
Enzo…
What is he talking--
What have you been telling
this arrogant guy?
Why is he talking to me like that?
Have you been badmouthing me?
Mom, people can hear you.
And what right do you have
to talk to my daughter like that?
Here?
Wow! Wow!
What a perfect mother!
-Mom… that's enough.
-Go on.
Do it. Make a scene.
Show everyone your true colors.
I'm not the one making a scene.
You are!
You're the one who humiliated a man
in front of so many people.
Mom…
Me?
Martin and I are engaged!
And you will die of envy!
Mom…
You're so shameless.
Let go of me!
Don't you dare lay a finger
on my daughter!
I may have put up with everything,
but not that!
You think you've taken
everything from me, Carlota?
No matter what you do,
you can't hide the truth.
That you ruined my family
when you chose to become
Martin's mistress.
Mom…
I thought you and Dad got together
after he and Mom broke up?
Mom.
Patricia…
I raised you, didn't I?
You should believe me.
But what's the truth?
You're shameless.
Who's more shameless?
I caught you and Martin
together back then.
My husband and I split up
because of you, remember?
You destroyed our family!
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry, dear.
Why aren't you all answering?
Sweetie, what's wrong?
I thought you and Mom Carlota
only got together
after you and Mom separated?
Did you cheat on Mom?
It wasn't that simple, Patricia.
I asked you a yes-or-no question, Dad.
Your mother and I had been
having problems for a long time.
She was always focused on the company.
She stopped being a wife and a mother.
You know that, don't you?
Why didn't you just leave her
if you weren't happy anymore?
Why did you have to cheat on her?
I had to choose between the two of you.
Do you know how hard it was for me?
I chose you because I thought…
Mom was the only one at fault.
Why did you destroy our family?
I thought you understood!
You let me grow up without her.
I've had to squeeze myself
into the family you and Mom Carlota built!
Patricia, you know that's not true.
Carlota treats you like her own daughter!
Come on, Pa…
You know that's not true.
She treats me differently
from her own children.
But I understood that.
I understood your situation.
Because I didn't want
to make things harder for you.
Because I wanted you to be happy.
What's this, Patricia?
Are you throwing a fit
because of what you found out?
One word from your mother,
and you've forgotten everything
your Dad and I did for you?
Why did you destroy our family?
Why did you choose to be a mistress?
Carlota!
You ingrate!
So what if I was a mistress?
This mistress is the one who raised you!
Are you going to forget all the sacrifices
your Dad and I made for you?
Who raised you from the time
you were a child?
Well, I'm sorry.
I convinced myself
that you saw me as your daughter.
If you really saw me as your daughter,
you wouldn't hold those things
over my head.
How dare you talk back? Patricia!
Why'd you have to hit Patricia?
This is your fault.
What are you saying?
If you'd married me back then,
she wouldn't call me a mistress!
You let me become the other woman!
Patricia…
Let me explain.
I know you don't understand.
I was scared.
I didn't want you to hate me.
I couldn't bear losing you.
All my life, Dad…
I did everything your family wanted.
I gave everything I had…
I gave everything I had,
even when I had nothing left.
Because I thought…
I'd be a part of your family
as long as I was useful to you.
Patricia, that's not true.
I love all of you…
I love you so much, Dad.
I want to believe
I made the right decision back then…
when I chose to go with you.
But did I make a mistake…
in choosing you, Dad?
I was angry at Mom for so long.
I hated her for so long…
Patricia, that's not true…
Because I truly believed she was the one
who destroyed our family.
Why did you do that, Pa?
Why did you lie to me?
I only did that because…
I was afraid of losing you.
Your mother had everything.
She could've easily taken you
away from me back then.
I'm powerless.
I had no chance against her.
I had no chance.
I'm sorry.
Patricia…
Is that really the reason, Dad?
Or did you use me as a prize
just so you could feel like
you'd won against Mom?
No, dear. It's not like that.
The initial terms look promising.
Right, Ms. Aragon?
So, I guess that's it for this meeting.
-Okay.
-Thank you.
Sure.
-Let's go?
-Let's go.
Benjie, I'm heading out now.
Hi.
Sandra.
What are you doing here?
Oh, I'm meeting a friend who's interested
in buying Ricardo's place.
Ricardo had to leave earlier
than expected, so I'm handling the sale.
Ricardo is leaving?
Um, I actually called him,
and he is on his way to the airport.
Didn't he tell you?
ISABELLE CHAVEZ
BORN: AUG. 16 2007 DIED: OCT. 23 2022
Uh… Excuse me.
How are you related to the deceased?
Who are you?
I have a friend in the US.
He said that his daughter is buried here.
He wanted me to check.
This one. Isabelle Chavez.
We have no relatives in America.
You must have gotten it wrong.
Ms. D, it looks like we won't be able
to get to the airport.
The traffic is very heavy.
Ma'am, I'm sorry.
But are you sure?
My friend told me
that his daughter died of cancer.
My daughter died because of an accident.
Who's the friend you're talking about?
Ricardo Salvador? Do you know him?
I don't know him.
This guy.
I'm sorry, but I really don't know him.
What about you, sir?
I've seen him before.
I've seen him a few times
when I'd bring flowers
for your daughter, ma'am.
There's a grave he visits.
Then tell him.
Sir, follow me.
This one, sir.
-Okay. Thank you.
-Okay.
I made the recipe! It came from me!
I'm telling the truth!
You are thieves!
Ricardo?
Diana.
I thought you already left.
Why are you here?
I-I don't know either.
Diana, I don't know what you did to me.
With everything that has happened to me,
I have long accepted
that I will be alone in life.
But because of you,
I had the hope of being happy again.
But now I feel…
devastated.
Because I'm not good enough
to be loved by you.
I don't want you to feel that way.
I didn't mean to.
I'm so sorry.
You know, I don't want to go. But if…
if I'm not worth anything to you anymore…
there is no reason for me to stay here.
I understand.
Ricardo.
Patricia.
April.
What's happening between you
and Mom and Dad?
Mom said you had an argument.
Don't worry about it.
It will pass.
Patricia, are you mad at us?
N-No.
I know that you were hurt.
But, Patricia, I want you to know that I…
have never thought of you differently.
You're my family.
I know it's hard that you
have to be responsible for me and Jena.
That's why I'm studying hard…
so that when I graduate,
I'll help you.
So you can achieve your dreams
that you have set aside for our sake.
I am so thankful
for all the sacrifices you made for us.
That's so nice to hear.
Hey.
I did that…
because I love you.
You two are my sisters.
And that will never change.
Thank you, sis.
Clara.
-Yes?
-Has Mom arrived?
She's not here yet.
-Huh?
-What? Why isn't she here yet?
I called and texted her,
but she wasn't answering.
What about you, Sir Enzo?
Wait.
There are no messages from her.
That's weird.
She'd usually inform us
if she won't come to work, right?
Actually, yes.
She just probably woke up late.
Enzo, Mom is never late.
She's almost always the first one
to arrive here.
-Take these to the laundry room.
-Okay. All right.
Thank you.
-Hello?
-Hello, Nanny Cora?
Is Mom there?
No, she's not here.
She didn't come home last night.
Why?
She had Benjie drive her somewhere,
then sent him home.
Did she say where she's going?
To Ricardo's house.
Patricia isn't with you?
No.
I didn't see her all day.
I think she's avoiding me.
She's still upset with me.
But I can't blame her.
If I was in her place, I'd get upset too.
If I had just told her
when she was younger,
maybe she wouldn't get hurt this much.
Are you saying it's wrong
for us to be together?
-Carlota…
-The way I see it,
you regret ever being with me!
I never said anything like that.
You never say it,
but that's what you think, right?
It's exhausting waiting for you
to choose me for once!
You know what I went through
with Diana's family!
I've looked up to them
since I was a child,
especially to Diana herself.
Then, you came into my life.
And even with you,
I still feel like a beggar!
I thought I could have you
all for myself, Martin!
That we can have a happy family together…
but I was wrong.
Carlota…
Hey, Patricia, everything will be fine.
The police are on standby
in case Ms. D doesn't respond
within tonight.
Why won't she tell us where she is?
Come here.
Hey…
Don't worry too much, okay?
Patricia?
Sir, good evening.
"I'LL EXPLAIN EVERYTHING, DEAR.
WE'LL TALK WHEN I GET HOME."
-It's Mom.
-Why?
What happened to Diana?
Boss.
Find out what Ricardo has to do
with Cecilia Pineda.
And I want this information
as soon as possible.
Copy, boss.
Mom!
Patricia.
What happened to you?
You were gone for days!
I'm fine, dear. I'm fine.
What's the important thing
we need to talk about?
Diana!
What's this nonsense?
I was worried--
Patricia was worried sick!
Take it easy, Martin.
What did you do to Diana?
We only wanted to talk with Patricia.
You little…
Sir? We don't need
to make a scene here, please.
Whatever you need to tell Patricia,
I need to know, too.
I'm not leaving without my daughter.
And I won't shut up until you speak.
This is a family matter.
You arrogant bastard.
-Who do you think you are?
-Sir!
Martin.
Let go of my husband.
We're married.
UNCLE TEDDY
I hope you will be happy for us.
Because I'm happy.
If something needs to be hidden,
that means something is wrong with it.
The way she acts right now…
Very out of character for her.
If Mom loves and trusts you,
don't expect the same from me.
Patricia, I am not the enemy.
-Is Diana there?
-Yes.
Don't let her leave.
There's something she needs to know.
I want you to be happy,
but I also want you to be safe.